[music]
you can step
and yes, but how to make it stronger and here's
the picture
[music]
life meaning now should be better
heard
he is this guy this is the 7 step method
he is a substitute for proud as an activity
probably he always changed must change
himself to do an exchange himself that environment
by the way and show this
picture again guys
this is what we invented for lam rim and then about
years ago it is called [ __ ] no
one calls it that except me but
I hope that it will pick up and all this
means we eat it means image in business well yes
and the ball itar tass image of ideas this is
such a way to remember where the concept
visually works very well if you
meditate you can
we in this course 150 of these and inches we
will analyze if you between them this make a
connection such in the mind then you can without
opening your eyes at all meditate on
all this rubbish of rim just remember the
pictures and you can then
sit in this picture think stay on it do
not think what it means and what
we emphasize is the
diamond way we can accept this
pretend that we were not  The
vizier's methods with different angels
are very productive, so
try to understand why they sent you this
image, this image, and find the
image. Why am I mentioning this? Well,
it will be dark here. We will have a
competition, we will give them and Dimam.
Every time there will be this kind of competition.
We sprinkle you with each person
who
participates.
Find someone of your own. We see this on this
course and we will compare them. We have presentations.
Who can
remember? Who can forget?
[music] had a
very memorable presentation. There was such a party.
This was a party pill, which was
generally very funny. I remember. I
also voted for him.
We ask you to create your own
pictures. I'll tell you something
rather dry.
Counting hundreds of pages. Slam Remote.
Quite a spirit.
When I stop, I go
looking. We eat something wrong. He mentions
remembering. It's better to take off. And this slows you down.
Maybe there's too much there
during the time. There are six points in one, 12 in
another, and it will slow down
and descend. And Dima, you
have to think about this
meaning in order to choose a good picture. It
represents this. They can easily find a
suitable picture. There are a lot of them.  It takes
time, they
stood, they know,
you can probably do something quickly, but it won't
mean anything, and either you can
attack like that, by choosing,
we use
the site
1123,
RFR, f, which means
the road to free, but for
us it's outside, so you can
use my password, but not very good
quality, very good, such kind
pictures,
beautiful, all the pictures possible, which
you can only wish for, they are all on the
same site, they are of good quality,
high quality, and
walls, such a site as this guy with
muscles, for example,
usually it's just a photograph, well, in general,
Lvovich, you understand, so if you add the
teaching of Pooh,
equal rights, and
exchanging yourself over another, this I don't want,
I don't want to just hear, exchanging yourself for
others, it's always equal rights in the beginning,
and then amine yourself against others, this
makes
your
development stronger, your 7-step would distinguish, and
further along the way,
we will cut off, we talked about this, this 7-step theme,
develop, distinguish, what definition will
cure, and for 100 dollars
[music]
answer the question,
come on, let's give
50 to each, let's be
democratic,
you can try to achieve this
desire by taking seven steps from  In
fact, there are seven and a half
before or you can use
equal rights and exchange in them
something interesting is happening
now we have
something interesting happened in the history
with the console cycle the teaching on exchanging oneself for
others
was it was considered secret it is
not the same as to dump
listen
there and
there yes this is a
Tibetan different chip and I have
chipidip
I bought a chip chip
chip it is cheap
in German and
different in Tibetan words
this is the
hippie movement exactly thousands of years ago
it was what kind of hippie movement was there
in Tibet and in fact well that's what
they were called and
since then they have had nothing like that
except 60 and
here
it means it was
saved it was accepted secret
receives the admin method of exchanging oneself for others
what we what we have not talked about yet this is
not how it sounds
it was considered secret but the secret was
kept only this is part 1 through
which there were no such secret it
was equal rights
clearly further he says that this is very
interesting if you know Tibetan
these children's writings linden linden
what they said this practice of
exchanging oneself for  others and
that damn that
100 bucks
sometimes
people give an answer to a 100 spiritual question
further before I asked
another question don't forget to request this from my
banker in fact this is a
tape he is correct in the beginning will take
and then you give in the beginning you take
other people's problems yourself
then you give that this practice of giving
and
taking and
expensive he says that they were connected
and they were
separate separated as a very high
practice almost secret which
was called 300 thieves 500 dollars someone
told you
I'm glad that
thousands announcing
I never layers
John this is an attempt to
develop would you count a good heart that is
he says that
it was created these 2 secret practices the
first
is the one who on the table or
2 was 100 rubles and the first exchange yourself
other
interesting equation
take one of the others add a toilet
and
collecting firewood more than others and gave them
happiness is equal to lodging this is a very
interesting idea very attractive
so that in this not studied in the essay this is number
14 elegance why I do on
logic Alabin
students loss I had 80  There are
40 left,
we just need something to bring people back. I
then said, then I made a jong, they didn't
come back, or
here this equation of exchanging others
plus giving and
taking is equal to developing a kind
heart. It's very interesting, and I
think she has beauty. This idea came to
me, although it looks too serious
for this practice,
and
this was, by the way, the next next thing.
Apparently, this is lodging.
People are bringing the wrong
ear, and
how
[music]
some people
use this word, ladronka, it
pleases me very much,
like
enlightened minds, but John, or
training the mind
or a kind heart. These girls are
lodging against the police. 3 who is crying,
this is
oh, training, moog, uhh, uhh. Someone,
this sounds like some kind of Nazis.
Brainwashing. Don't forget this. 3 of
a mind. Yes, you, this is exactly what hurts me very much
when I hear this.
The post is so important. Please remember
when you
hear
this word, lodging, [ __ ], picture for
Luchenka.
They do it better, carry it,
they don't train, and Judas and his soul doesn't
just show vibrations,
then it leaves.  How do you practice this
exchange of yourself for others?
How should we practice
our money?
Practice is also small and
doomed, she said, or
dart conduction?
Further, also j,
this proves that there are two steps:
equal rights and exchange north from others
because here he says
exchange here in others, he does not say
equal rights and exchange. Singer, did you understand?
There is a big difference between the one who gave the gel and
so Shinji
because the word that we usually have, if
Shinji and you are
needed, creatures, as equal rights, what,
fortunately, and then this is from the place of others.
Now he pulled out Dakshi
G&G, which means exchange, exchange, exchange
from others. If you want to talk about how
to exchange others, let's look at
avatars
2. If his containers are known,
0 dollars,
so easy, and that I will not pay
more than
450 for it. They started an avatar,
but how
to transform, how to
get this identity next, therefore, this
film is an avatar,
put on this identity when
Joan Jay,
if you want to protect yourself and
others quickly between quickly, then
pushes, exchange yourself for others,
than so, is the owl
high, well, and those who know, he knows
diesel fuel, secret practice, who
causes this secret  Shanti Levo practice
[music]
it's like a friendly warm
shower and the guy says you know, do you
really want a secret practice?
Just practice exchanging yourself for others.
Got it?
He's right about it. He doesn't call for it. It's a very
secret practice. It's a
whole, even high-high
secret archive. All you want to do is
exchange yourself for others. If
you really want to help others, then
exchange other people. This is the
highest of all secret practices.
This is Santa D.Va. He says that this means
it's such a final secret.
This is the topic of a child. Yes, no, his hair is
too straight.
Why am I eating this? I chose what I want. So
you tell me what it's like.
Guess
what number it is.
Why
will it be high on 4? The practice of
exchanging yourself for others is
one aspect.
If you do it well, don't
brag. But in this, like I do somewhere,
I'm a slingshot.
She noticed something. Let's go then.
She didn't say, exchange others. She didn't
say,
put yourself in
another person's shoes, in another
person's shirt, and then you will feel how
difficult it is. Thousands of trees to judge. She
said.  Place yourself in the body of Geshe Michael
and look back on
eBay. You will do it, Michael, and not only that,
you will feel
sympathy for this hard work that
someone,
for example, there with thousands of trees and
the elements plants 444 thousand
units. This does not mean an exchange from you to
others. This does not mean
placing yourself in the skin of another person and
his shoes and you will feel it. It means
becoming an anti-
kill person and
look at yourself through his eyes and
then you will understand how you look to
other people. Sometimes in this rent, in
fact,
it would be completely scary. It is
difficult to understand how
we are protected karmically so that
all day long and are forced to be considered
smarter than other people. We think that it is good that we are
protected, protected by such an
ability. It is normal that this is very
scary. It is very difficult to
hear, in fact, to hear, but here,
other shoes, for example, you can go
sell your car to buy a
MAZ and at
that time you can,
Olenka, and you do something
to live and
I say that I am a cook in the
temple and then you hear how this guy looks like
we are some kind of fool, that is,
you read  me where you are and I think
it's just very
heightened, so it should be
kept a secret only people like people
who are quite mature spiritually can
endure and if they
hear that each of those
people in the room with them thinks about
them, it can be just depressing to
get to know a
friend, this is also part of this
stage, we're going and this one, let's show you
again
to the goal, your Dima, and I want you to
do this for what,
why was it secret, it
seems so basic, let's
express it so friendly,
put yourself in the skin of another person,
this
if it can be simply
incredible, this we are simply beyond your powers
and
then you might not be able to
improve
I
[music]
Dana, you can say that
your idea of ​​me as a goat is
actually about surrender and we can improve there,
but it would simply be
mentally greater than our strength if you
could hear the thoughts of other people, we have and
probably a lot of people who are super weight
and
probably they have such an ability
to hear that other people may be a
lot of crazy people, they are just super
sensitive, super sensitive, this is for
them
mental capabilities of forces, this
means them people who will not be
able to cope and
this
means this is not  A worthy vessel would have
taught them by force,
it was beyond their ability if
they actually heard what others
thought of them,
Lorca, quieter,
as it means, banknotes,
he conveyed this to Chicago, quieter, conveyed this,
sorry, quieter.
During this period, this
was preserved, meaning hidden, they did
not teach this publicly, and they
passed it on to those people whom they considered
already spiritually mature enough to
hear the thoughts of other people. The tailbone is
now a picture, tell me why this
has anything to do with this. The picture is
Cesar from eco-friendly, we say
this in the quality of a cup, that is, three,
three pictures of a cup, three images.
This would be too much water, and
this vessel would overflow.
This person's thought would not be able to
hold it.
It would really not sit down.
If they began to hear voices,
other people's heads have it in them and theirs,
and it would be full, and part of the edge of their
vessels would spill over. This means that they would go crazy.
So let's do this, let's
only teach this. This sang their
students who have the ability.
I tolerate that they didn't want people to
go crazy like a pit,
even 35 years old. Gin, brandy,
his team walks and searches for
old books. Ancient Frank, large for
tags of the world, himself, more for St. Petersburg,
by the way,
Russian, and very
deep in terms of books.
I went there in 1995 to
negotiate.
I was on the metro and there were all the
businessmen there and others who were there. The metro.
They were reading Dostoevsky's books,
for example, even if they were there
on the subway, it simply allows their
love for deep ideas.
Russian people are very deep and they
read different books. The
only one in the world who has
very carefully preserved
Sanskrit books since the time of the Tsar for 500 years in a
warehouse and
warehouse. Hami. This warehouse is the
palace of the
ancient Tsar.
They kept ancient Tibetan books there.
Several thousand of these books are the most beautiful in the
country. St. Petersburg. They
were cataloged there. It is
incredibly
powerful and, in response to requests, sometimes there is a seal. The
only one who can do this seal. On
some, there is
someone who can blame or, sadly, on the outside, this is the
abbot of the monastery. This
means that it is actually imprinted. This
means that they are
physically sealed. That is, the Pinegas
exchanged from themselves to others.
They were sealed.
There is a beautiful painting by John Brandy and
Plan Hee. I was
hiding there in K from that plane. As long as
my family, through these, like
this, flew through these mountains, and
John is also already ill. You are no longer there.
Finally, there is something interesting going on. John has been there for
35 years.  and so they decided to
keep it as a pit from this period
between Larka's mother-in-law
582 years 2
actor
current
means mother
destroy
this will not say why
you
never went to noticed
[music]
on pancakes and transform
poison from plants and poisonous into the
color of beautiful feathers the end he from think you
fly
peacock and eat
I David and plants 25 dollars they
go from
choose to be at any age and what is Shado that
with separate and you shoot or can
Sanskrit it will start with and this is the month of
speeds yours means not that is they
say where it is more
convenient
cultivates Dasha and
they
ignore Ashada and they eat I David
plants a miracle this is all you are here around
trying
you here we have two
I David
ova-1 there is no such thing they braided
it before they used it as this ancient
Vedic
this was accepted
plant here
maybe
I say there be their I before this
peacocks only live on these plants and
not only in feathers they turn into a
beautiful color of feathers
[music]
can
this allows you to
look better like Ukrainians who
They take on themselves and others in
nature and they transform this into non-violence
for the whole world, this is the beauty of this, the
beauty of this, peacocks,
there is the famous La Jonu, which is
called a
peacock, which destroys this type of
plant by eating them, distinguishes the poison in these
plants, that is, it is cool
[music] to
take away bad emotions in other people,
for example, and turn it into something
good, for example, someone comes and is
irritated, and you will be able to
transform it into something pleasant,
good for everyone, a beautiful
short practice called
oil
and stalker,
there is even a refugee, he is
Syrian, he is Siamese, this is
Siji, they are a very handsome son,
snore, a
refugee, a
Sufi poet,
together with the practice in public, it is very
beautiful, a very
famous
Muslim
author in Russia, we will analyze Arbekov, we
will have it this year too, also a beautiful, very
beautiful
marriage, Rumiya, and 3 will not be and the text is very
beautiful, she
translates Rumi, I directly from Arabic,
she
was in Persian, and here we
translate Arabic,
but
this practice
expands the expansion of
this practice  pablina
jindon don 7 private jong
you private practice for development
came
all this it was wonderful to
be
if you practice this specific
text scene drawing
together this is a very interesting word and
what is
forcibly stronger than
anything else interesting word it is as
if forcibly stronger much more powerful
that is and improving to improve you better
not your heart will be
forcibly powerful and others
to achieve and son I offer you this teaching
this does not mean
these
practices are lazy loot that they were
secret they were they were passed down
oral traditions they were
passed down in rhymed poetry that
is you will then be able to understand that you
missed a line
I
thought Jackie thought he would return that
is if you
skip words it will be dzyk dzyk dzyk dzyk
with which there is no back that is to
jump into
ancient times that was orally
transmitted and
I have an original copy about a blogger
almost
10 years ago
this means I have one of the
original pi yao you this of they with
this  I
promise that the first thing that was written
was something verbally, so long time,
some say 1500 years and from a time
where there are many options, each
student I will remember this is wrong, but
differently, incorrectly, differently at once in
advertising,
let the Japanese have such a game, there was a broken
telephone, there were more, you whisper to someone, 1 on
another, a third, and at the end, it is always completely
changed completely, the
principle is
a picture of how
many people came to us on a horse
from Tucson, who, how many of you on a horse with
Oleg didn't even ride, I can't believe it,
why didn't we come here on a
horse? Because
cars are almost that, he is very furiously
more
efficient, more powerful,
anyone can take it
in three hours in an air-conditioned car with
amenities than to ask days on a horse,
this is
GSM, what was previously with horses, why
guard it and even early John Gamma,
she is they are more powerful, seconds, more
violently, a bullet, powerfully
favorable
g I personally prefer the presentation
quicksilver and I am
silent,
meaning silver, it also means water,
sometimes Thursday is
important in Buddhism, Mercury
was used for newborn little ones
Non-
toxic quantities to
turn iron into gold, alchemy is based on this, it's
very toxic, very dangerous, so no,
try
everyone
if you want to
buy it, it won't work.
Lama Quiksilver, this translates
to the actual plant Arma Badra,
he took up postcards, even though he was in
Tibet, Tibet,
Quicksilver Dorma game,
he
wrote a
good comment, and he
wrote two comments on your genes,
one of them
in the Mount domain, not he's a cheater on Badra, his
spiritual son,
he also didn't write a comment on the road,
also now they translated it from him, it's worth it,
I asked, hung up,
we heard that they released it with partners, is this
normal for a monk, I sent them
Yanuk, having printed out a list of books about this
hotelier practice and career,
case
500 thunder can very and
17,000 commentary in the
form, maybe this is normal, didn't they say
we
translated 15,000 pages,
Lakra, excellent work, probably, we
did it well, maybe
everything wrote some of the best
comments, they are
wonderful, they are magnificent, and I
will also follow the same method,
he even had a legal partner,
this is the line
was  I
will be sealed, dollar yes, quieter
[music]
982 dota hour
52 years was it a secret
practice because it would be one-time in
people
also great students
from quieter who are
doctors and lord quieter very much
in I am a lama in our line who
never became a monk, he was a
businessman,
but he
could start, we will tell you these I think that he is
very important as an example
for modern people of modern times,
you do not have to be a monk or a
nun in our culture to be a
great teacher of miracles and
in our culture it will probably be more
effective
to be a businessman, they
began to teach their
students as a monk after a century, we break it down, paclan, do you go on,
that is, they
began to teach it publicly 10 I appoint a group of
students hame
[music]
then parts were secrets, the
main ones in pure Rome was it was
taught publicly here is jong, part of
Jenga was taught
privately, but together, that is, in the temple of
Schlitz to get am Rome and the
teacher, if he thought you were ready,
you passed jong honestly,
that is, from secret years they came to
visit  So,
when
Lam-rim became
hybrid,
they taught hybrid teachings.
Some parts were rhetorical,
some gases, and the
track was open. This is Lam-li.
If you're at
home and think about the Diamond Korea teachings,
stupid pictures. You
understand what happened. Sojin, you know, at that
time, that part of things is secret, but they
started teaching us Rim
openly. It was a hybrid ghoul. What
happens after that? They
completely regenerated the gas, and
now we
have this teaching at Jong-gu openly.
I hope you remember this. It's better not to
try anymore. But often, my team
goes on break and I'll see you at Jong-gu's. Here,
Jong-gu
and the students say it's
very difficult to catch.
And at night,
we had a competition here and a
split for
this guy. Harut won.
Think that I
stole it, but I want to stay in the
palace for now.
I'm
not just him in the debate. I watched him in the debate. He even has a
plaza de bo terom, not just good
creators. Dimam